<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Introduction on Showcase Template</title><link>https://visualcomputing.github.io/showcase/</link><description>Recent content in Introduction on Showcase Template</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://visualcomputing.github.io/showcase/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title/><link>https://visualcomputing.github.io/showcase/docs/About-Us/Alejandro_M/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://visualcomputing.github.io/showcase/docs/About-Us/Alejandro_M/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://visualcomputing.github.io/showcase/docs/coloring/coloring/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://visualcomputing.github.io/showcase/docs/coloring/coloring/</guid><description>HSL Color Mode # HSL Color Mode es una manera de representar colores en términos de tres propiedades: Matiz, saturación y luminosidad. El HSL Color Mode esta basado en el concepto de la rueda de color, donde los colores están organizados en un círculo de acuerdo con su matiz. El matiz es medido en grados, con rojo en 0°, verde en 120° y azul en 240° y todos los demás matices organizados entre los tres colores primarios.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://visualcomputing.github.io/showcase/docs/illusions/illusions/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://visualcomputing.github.io/showcase/docs/illusions/illusions/</guid><description>Ilusiones # Ilusiones Opticas # Las ilusiones ópticas son imágenes capaces de engañar al cerebro desde las imágenes generadas en los sensores oculares, y llevan a percibir la realidad de manera distorsionada.
Estas distorsiones se producen principalmente cuando se presentan múltiples imágenes diferentes concentradas en una única, lo que genera que el cerebro entre en conflicto al no comprender como interpretar de manera coherente alguna percepción de color, forma, movimiento o textura.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://visualcomputing.github.io/showcase/docs/masking/masking/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://visualcomputing.github.io/showcase/docs/masking/masking/</guid><description> Kernels de imagenes # Teclas Especiales Tecla Description F Cambiar mascara G Mostrar histograma H Cambiar imagen V Disminuir brillo B Aumentar brillo R Resetear imagen</description></item><item><title/><link>https://visualcomputing.github.io/showcase/docs/terrain_generation/mach_bands/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://visualcomputing.github.io/showcase/docs/terrain_generation/mach_bands/</guid><description>Terrain with Perlin Noise # Perlin Noise is used here to represent the &amp;ldquo;natural&amp;rdquo; change in incerted triangles in a plane
Perlin Noise # Perlin Noise es un tipo de función de ruido procedimental, lo que significa que genera valores aleatorios de forma que parezcan naturales y orgánicos. Fue inventado por Ken Perlin en 1983 para su uso en gráficos por ordenador.
Perlin Noise genera una cuadrícula de valores, en la que cada punto de la cuadrícula tiene asignado un valor aleatorio.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://visualcomputing.github.io/showcase/docs/About-Us/David_Cifuentes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://visualcomputing.github.io/showcase/docs/About-Us/David_Cifuentes/</guid><description> David Alejandro Cifuentes Gonzalez # I&amp;rsquo;m a Systems engenering student at Universidad Nacional de Colombia, I&amp;rsquo;m from Bogota-Colombia and I&amp;rsquo;m currently coursing the sixth semester of the carrer
My carrer development aspirations
Data Science AI Project Management Hobbies
Tennis Guitar/Piano Overthing stuff Music</description></item><item><title/><link>https://visualcomputing.github.io/showcase/docs/terrain_generation/coloring/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://visualcomputing.github.io/showcase/docs/terrain_generation/coloring/</guid><description>Coloring a sphere with HSB color model # HSB Color Mode # HSB Color Mode una manera de representar colores usando tres valores: Matiz, saturación y brillo. HSB significa Matiz, Saturación y Brillo por sus siglas en inglés (Hue, Saturation, and Brightness) y aveces también se le llama HSV (Hue, Saturation, Value).
En HSB Color Mode el matiz todavía se representa por una rueda de color donde los colores son organizados en un círculo de acuerdo a su ángulo de matiz.</description></item><item><title/><link>https://visualcomputing.github.io/showcase/docs/About-Us/Juan_Fontecha/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://visualcomputing.github.io/showcase/docs/About-Us/Juan_Fontecha/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Creating a New Theme</title><link>https://visualcomputing.github.io/showcase/posts/creating-a-new-theme/</link><pubDate>Sun, 28 Sep 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://visualcomputing.github.io/showcase/posts/creating-a-new-theme/</guid><description>Introduction # This tutorial will show you how to create a simple theme in Hugo. I assume that you are familiar with HTML, the bash command line, and that you are comfortable using Markdown to format content. I&amp;rsquo;ll explain how Hugo uses templates and how you can organize your templates to create a theme. I won&amp;rsquo;t cover using CSS to style your theme.
We&amp;rsquo;ll start with creating a new site with a very basic template.</description></item><item><title>Migrate to Hugo from Jekyll</title><link>https://visualcomputing.github.io/showcase/posts/migrate-from-jekyll/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Mar 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://visualcomputing.github.io/showcase/posts/migrate-from-jekyll/</guid><description>Move static content to static # Jekyll has a rule that any directory not starting with _ will be copied as-is to the _site output. Hugo keeps all static content under static. You should therefore move it all there. With Jekyll, something that looked like
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ images/ logo.png should become
▾ &amp;lt;root&amp;gt;/ ▾ static/ ▾ images/ logo.png Additionally, you&amp;rsquo;ll want any files that should reside at the root (such as CNAME) to be moved to static.</description></item><item><title>(Hu)go Template Primer</title><link>https://visualcomputing.github.io/showcase/posts/goisforlovers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://visualcomputing.github.io/showcase/posts/goisforlovers/</guid><description>Hugo uses the excellent Go html/template library for its template engine. It is an extremely lightweight engine that provides a very small amount of logic. In our experience that it is just the right amount of logic to be able to create a good static website. If you have used other template systems from different languages or frameworks you will find a lot of similarities in Go templates.
This document is a brief primer on using Go templates.</description></item><item><title>Getting Started with Hugo</title><link>https://visualcomputing.github.io/showcase/posts/hugoisforlovers/</link><pubDate>Wed, 02 Apr 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://visualcomputing.github.io/showcase/posts/hugoisforlovers/</guid><description>Step 1. Install Hugo # Go to Hugo releases and download the appropriate version for your OS and architecture.
Save it somewhere specific as we will be using it in the next step.
More complete instructions are available at Install Hugo
Step 2. Build the Docs # Hugo has its own example site which happens to also be the documentation site you are reading right now.
Follow the following steps:</description></item></channel></rss>